Compared to physical health, people tend
to pay less attention to their mental
health issue and are less willing to ask for help.
People who are lack of emotion
regulation strategies and have emotion
dysregulation problems are more affected
by high pressure.
Besides, emotion regulation as a potentially unifying function
of diverse symptom presentations and maladaptive behaviors.
Sometimes I am overly
emotional and unable to think rationally
so I feel that I need emotional
management.
I often feel depressed because of my boss's blame,
and sometimes even hurt myself.
Sometimes I even get angry because of small things that others don't care about.
People around me said that my mood is very ups and downs,
so they don’t dare to persuade me when I am emotional.
When I go to complain to my friends, they often don't understand my feelings.
They think that I am often too emotional about small things.
If I am in a bad mood, I will relieve myself by writing a diary.
I would like to find someone to talk
about things that make me depressed
however I usually can't find someone
willing to listen.
After interviewed some of our target users and a counseling psychologist who
who works at the Center of Counseling in National Chiao Tung University. We found
that they transfer their attention from things bothering them when bad mood
affect their daily life. They met barriers while contacting other people
when they want to have a conversation
with other people. Some people try to
suppress their feeling without aware of it
may cause emotional breakdowns.
Thus, we want to help them express their emotions by
chatting, self-recording and emotion reminding.
To achieve this goal, we develop an APP called "Euthymia".
When some people was in a bad mood, they couldn't find
a friend to talk with.
Since they might be busy doing something else or
didn't pick up their phone.
We allow users to enter chat themes for the emotion problem or find help from
others by starting a conversation.
We provide 10 best-fit people according to
the chat themes based on different features such as post-scoring and characteristics.
Users can chat with an AR animal which is actually a real person.
Post-scoring system can collect data and help improving our matching.
Users are allowed to record their daily thoughts by words or multimedia
By selecting the time you want to look at, we can show
your emotion proportion by daily, monthly or yearly.
Users can add diaries by a specific day,
using words, images and videos to record an event corresponding to an emotion emoji.
Our reminding system is able to connect users emotion diary and remind them
whether they might be in a high pressure later.
Users can also click on the notification and connect to our analyzing system.
Users can view which emotional state they are in
when their pressure signals are at a high peak.
They can also connect to diaries of the same emotion emoji,
knowing which previous events may cause this stress.
If the user's current mood is about to break through the threshold,
the physiological bracelet will vibrate to remind the user.
Euthymia brings users three main functions to help them
regulate their emotions, and build a relationship with other people.